Switchmen's Union of North America Records 5034
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings; Correspondence with Deming, H.H.-VanHeek, J.C. (Box 78)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 26)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 27)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1953 (Box 78, Folder 28)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 29)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 30)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 31)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 32)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 33)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1954 (Box 78, Folder 34)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Files Concerning Board of Directors Meetings, 1955 (Box 78, Folder 35)
    Proposed Amendments to Constitution
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - H.H. Deming, 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 36)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - F.H. Doty, 1960-1961 (Box 78, Folder 37)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1966-1969 (Box 78, Folder 38)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1965-1966 (Box 78, Folder 39)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Eugene C. Gertz, 1965 (Box 78, Folder 40)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - H.P. Watson, 1960-1964 (Box 78, Folder 41)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - H.P. Watson, 1959-1964 (Box 78, Folder 42)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - N.F. Anderson, 1966 (Box 78, Folder 43)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Milton Plumb Associates, 1966-1968 (Box 78, Folder 44)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 45)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 46)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 47)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 48)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 49)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 50)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 51)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 52)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 53)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 54)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 55)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 56)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 57)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - Neil Speirs, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 58)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 59)
    Minutes, Reports, Resolutions
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 60)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 61)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 62)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 63)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 64)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 65)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 66)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 67)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 68)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 69)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 70)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 71)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 72)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 73)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 74)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 75)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 78, Folder 76)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 77)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 78)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 79)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence - J.C. Van Heek, 1959-1969 (Box 78, Folder 80)
- Board of Directors Minutes, Reports, Correspondence (Box 79)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    Minutes, Reports, Correspondence
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 22)
    Correspondence, Minutes, Reports
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 38)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 79, Folder 39)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 40)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 42)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 43)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 44)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 45)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 46)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 47)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966-1968 (Box 79, Folder 48)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 49)
    Finance and Insurance Board Reports
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 50)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 51)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 52)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 53)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 54)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 55)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 56)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 57)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1955-1959 (Box 79, Folder 58)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 59)
    Finance and Insurance Board - Reports and Correspondence
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 60)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 61)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 62)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 63)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 64)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 65)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 66)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 67)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 68)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 69)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 70)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 71)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 72)
- Miscellaneous Reports, Membership Files, and Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer (Box 80)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1951-1967 (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1966 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    Membership of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1965 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    Membership of Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    Membership of Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Switchmen's Union of North America, and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    Membership of the Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen, Order of Railway Conductors, Switchmen's Union of North America, and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 15)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - General Secretary-Treasurer Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Charles Luna, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Charles Luna, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Charles Luna, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - N.P. Speirs, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - E.L. Stevens, 1966-1969 (Box 80, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - E.L. Stevens, 1966-1969 (Box 80, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer E.L. Stevens, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - E.L. Stevens, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Murphy, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 26)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Ernst and Ernst, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 27)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer- Ernst and Ernst, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 28)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Ernst and Ernst, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 29)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - J.H. Shepard, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 30)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - J.H. Shepard, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 31)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - J.H. Shepard, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Cornell University, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Cornell University, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 34)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Cornell University, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Cornell University, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 36)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - F. Anderson, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 37)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - M. Herrins (Box 80, Folder 38)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    January 1969.
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Board of Directors, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Changes in Representation to United Transportation Union, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 41)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Legislative Fund Assessment, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 42)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Legislative Fund Assessment, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Legislative Reports, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Legislative Boards, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Headquarters Staff Locations, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 46)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence with W.T. Meredith, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 47)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Notices, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 48)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Notices, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 49)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - General Secretary-Treasurer Conference, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer with Lincoln Moving Company, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 51)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Officer Moving Costs, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 52)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer with K. Moore, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 53)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Officer Addresses, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 54)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Office Directory, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union General Secretary and Treasurer Meeting with Labor Department, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 56)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Collins Travel Receipts, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 57)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Federationist, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Legal Assistance, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 59)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Financial Statement, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 60)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Seminar (Educational), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 61)
    March 1969.
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning reduced dues, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 62)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Collins Per Diem expense claims, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Collins Personal (Auto Article), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 64)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - United Transportation Union Insurance Board, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 65)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Contents of General Secretary and Treasurer Files, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Unification Part I, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 67)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Unification Part I, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 68)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Unification Part II, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Unification Part II, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Unification Part II, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 71)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Implementation Agreement, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Implementation Agreement, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 73)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - American Railway Union Declaration of Principles, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 74)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence with Transportation Political Education League, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 75)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence with New York State Department of Labor, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 76)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Letter of Recommendation (John Obach), 1969 (Box 80, Folder 77)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Notice of United Transportation Union Financial Reporting, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 78)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Unification Vote, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 79)
    December 1968
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Remarks on United Transportation Union in Congressional Record, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 80)
    February 1969.
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Potential Consolidation of Locals, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 81)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Potential Consolidation of Locals, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 82)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Switchmen's Union of North America Transfer Book (Directory), 1968 (Box 80, Folder 83)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Disposition of Locals under Unification, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 84)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Disposition of Locals under Unification, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 85)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Disposition of Locals under Unification, 1968-1969 (Box 80, Folder 86)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Number of Members by Local, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 87)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Railroad Benefits, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 88)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence with Railroad Retirement Board, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 89)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence with Labor Newspaper, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 90)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Aetna Bon Cancellation, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 91)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - General Adjustment Committee Deficient Balances, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 92)
    December 1968.
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Employees Tax Withholding Certificates, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 93)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Employees Addresses, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 94)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Designation of Depository Correspondence concerning Switchmen's Union accounts, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 95)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Department of Labor Publications, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence, BRAC-ORC&B merger, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 97)
    Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks and Order of Railway Conductors and Brakemen
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Unification Convention Roster, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 98)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Resolutions of Unification, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 99)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Documents and Press Releases Unification, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 100)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Documents and Press Releases Unification, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 101)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Documents and Press Releases Unification, 1968 (Box 80, Folder 102)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 103)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 104)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 106)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 107)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 108)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Correspondence concerning Unification, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 109)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Special Adjustment Boards, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 110)
  - Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer - Brotherhood of Locomotive Fireman and Enginemen versus Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 1969 (Box 80, Folder 111)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence of General Secretary-Treasurer (Box 81)